<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Item>
  <Name id = 0002 "Frozen Snakes of Fire"</Name>
  <Type> Discovery & Survival Quest 3</Type>
  <Description >
	Herschel follows a strange infrared trail of a 
	thermal-hydro-snake, which slithers and spits 
	hot cryo-acid. It follows it into a cave 
	filled of snakes slithering and circling the probe. 
	Make it safely out of the cave.
  </Description>
  <Parts>

	<Part1>Take a look at this. Infrared scans are showing a
		strange pattern of isolated heat signatures 
		trailing across the sea floor. Follow the 
		infrared trail and see where it leads too.</Part2> 
	<Part2>Herschel Scans the First Trail Piece.</Part1>
	<Part3>This kind of heat signature is not caused by
		natural geography or weather. Evidence 
		suggests it must be organic in origin. 
		What could it be?</Part2> 
	<Part4>The heat intensity of these infrared signatures
		trails are increasing and becoming more frequent. 
		We must be getting closer to its source.</Part4>
	<Part5>This creature appears to be badly injured. 
		Judging by its wounds, it must have been attacked by another creature. 
		The noise it is making must be a cry for help, but it also increases 
		its chance of possibly being attacked again.</part5>
	<Part6>Reach Cave.</part6>
	<Part7>Numerous heat signatures of this similar trail
		pattern are leading directly into this cave.
		What could be inside?/Part7>
	<Part8>We’re detecting high acidity levels within the liquid hydrocarbon 
		of this cave. This cave could have form from cryovolcanic activity 
		in the past. Look! There is something up ahead.</Part8>
	<Part9>Reach Organism.</Part9>
	<Part10>Fascinating. Scans show that this life form lives off of the high 
		liquid acidity levels inside this cave, as well as numerous other 
		plants and microorganisms. The skeletal remains of previous organisms 
		here suggest that it use acid as a form of defense or means of digestion.</Part10>
	<Part11>Scan Eggs</Part11>
	<Part12>Looks like this snake hatched from these eggs. Knowing that there 
		are multiple eggs here, there could be more of these snake organisms 
		around.[SCREEEECH! Snakes appear and circle the probe like a tornado]</Part12>
	<Part13>It appears we have disturbed their nesting grounds, and they don’t 
		look very happy to see us! Quick! Get the probe to safety!</Part13>
	<Part14>[Exit cave to waypoint a hectometer outside] (If player dies, it will 
		spawn back in cave or back to nearest spawn point, and player will 
		have to go back to waypoint to complete mission]</Part14>
	<Part15>We have recorded as much information as we could about the cave and 
		snakes. That was quite the discovery. Good work.</Part15>
	<Part16> MISSION COMPLETE - Accolade Achieved: Snaaaaakes!</Part16>

  </Parts>
  <!-- This mission requires you to make a decision -->
</Item>