<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Item>
	<Name id = 0001 "Titan's Secret"</Name>
	<Type> Following Objective Quest</Type>
	<Description >
		Herschel is following main mission when the command
		center picks up a signal. This type of signal is 
		uncommon here on titan, for it hints at life on Titan.
		Herschel then follows the signal to discover it to be
		a crashed Chinese probe that was thought to be lost. 
	<Description>
	<Parts>
		<Part1>Mangled radio transmission is heard</Part2>
		<Part2>That's scientifically impossible! There 
			should be nothing on Titan transmitting; we
			are the first probe to land here successfully.
			There has to be a reason for this sort of 
			activity.</Part1>
		<Part3>...There is a frequency, but its signal is weak
			from your current location. I am sending you the 
			coordinates now.</Part2>
		<Part4>Move to coordinates provided</Part4>
		<Part5>**1/4 way there**
			We have done a full system diagnostics on Herschel;
			All systems are in working condition, and are fully 
			operational. These readings we are recieving are not
			due to on board malfunction.</Part5>
		</Part6>Continue to coordinates</Part6>
		</Part7>**1/2 way there**
			This is the only probe to visit and successfully
			land on Titan. The only mission before this was a
			Chinese probe to do just what Herschel is doing now.
			During its entry phase, a component malfunctioned
			and the landing boosters were not deployed. The 
			last readings on the probe showed it hitting the
			surface at speeds up to 400MPH. All equipment was
			assumed to be lost on impact, but it's the only
			reason we would be getting a signal like this.</Part7>
		</Part8>Continue to coordinates</Part8>
		</Part9>**3/4 way there**
			The signal source is coming from the bottom of the 
			ravine. Whatever the source, we are uncertain in what
			you will find down there.</Part9>
		</Part10>Explore the ravine for the source of the signal</Part10>
		</Part11>Scan the probe</Part11>
		</Part12>It seems it was the Chinese probe all this time,
			and it looks like it mostly survived impact. This is a 
			great find, and this will be valuable information to tell
			the Chinese Government that their probe was not completely 
			destroyed. We are just thankful it wasn't advanced alien
			life; that would be hard to cover up.MISSION OVER</Part12>
		
	</Parts>
</Item>