<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Item>
  <Name id = 0004 "That is No Iceberg!"</Name>
  <Type>Discovery Quest 4</Type>
  <Description >
	Herschel detects a large object nearby moving in the liquid. 
	It turns out to be icebergs. However, upon closer observations, 
	one of these icebergs is not an iceberg. It’s alive and moving! 
	Herschel follows the iceberg to a waterfall that sustains the iceberg creature.
  </Description>
  <Parts>

	<Part1>These wave ripples in the liquid hydrocarbon indicate activity in the 
		area. We are detecting a series of large slow-moving objects nearby. 
		Follow the source of the wave ripples.</Part1> 
	<Part2>[Herschel goes to group of icebergs after following 
		the wave ripples]</Part2>
	<Part3>Look at the size of these icebergs! Scan one of the 
		icebergs for closer analysis.</Part3> 
	<Part4>Scan Iceberg</Part4>
	<Part5>Scan complete. It appears these icebergs are made out of various 
		hydrocarbon mixtures frozen-packed together. 
		The iceberg is slowly melting by the warmer temperatures of the sea.</part5>
	<Part6>[LARGE ALIEN ICEBERG THINGAMABOB ARISES FROM UNDER WATER]</Part6>
	<Part7>Wait. We’re detecting more movement. Look at that! It
		appears one of the icebergs is moving! Wait… that’s not an iceberg.</Part7>
	<Part8>Use your long range scanner to safely analyze the creature.</Part8>
	<Part9>[BIOLOGICAL SCAN COMPLETE] Fascinating. It seems this creature 
		is using its iceberg-like appearance to camouflage itself amongst 
		the rest of the natural iceberg structures, possibly as a form of defense.</Part9>
	<Part10>[The iceberg creature moves away]</Part10>
	<Part11>It must be aware of our presence, since it is swimming away. Follow
			the creature. See where it is going</Part11>
	<Part12>[Creature leads to a waterfall]</Part12>
	<Part13>Amazing! The creature has lead us to what looks like a waterfall. 
			Let’s move closer to the waterfall for a liquid sample.</Part13>
	<Part14>[Sampling water]</Part14>
	<Part15>This waterfall is naturally flowing of liquid ethane and methane. 
			Further observation indicates that the creature is using the waterfall’s 
			liquid to help sustain its iceberg appearance, once frozen over time. 
			The waterfall could also be a source of food and mineral for the creature.</Part15>
	<Part16>What a fascinating discovery! [Mission Objective Complete]</Part16>
	<Part17>Accolade Achieved: That's No Iceberg!</Part17>
	


  </Parts>
  <!-- This mission requires you to make a decision -->
</Item>