<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Item>
  <Name id = 0005 "Help Me I'm Squshy"</Name>
  <Type> Hoard Defense Quest 5</Type>
  <Description >
	Herschel encounters a small creature that appears to be 
	injured from being attacked by another creature, 
	judging by its wounds. It seems to be calling out for help. 
	Out of sympathy and break of usual protocol, Herschel decides 
	to protect OR leave the creature alone. (protect) Protect the 
	creature from waves of enemies till its mom comes. (leave) the creature dies.
  </Description>
  <Parts>
	<Part1>A creature moans loudly in the distance</Part2> 
	<Part2>Can you hear that? Find out where that sound is coming from.</Part1> <!-- this is a child of a child-->
	<Part3>It looks like that creature up ahead is making that noise. Let’s take a closer look.</Part2> 
	<Part4>Scan the creature.</Part4>
	<Part5>This creature appears to be badly injured. 
		Judging by its wounds, it must have been attacked by another creature. 
		The noise it is making must be a cry for help, but it also increases 
		its chance of possibly being attacked again.</part5>
	<Part6>How should we proceed?</part6>
	<Part7A>CHOICE 1: I understand it is break of protocol, but we should protect the creature until help arrives.</part7A>
		<Part7A1>Very well, keep an eye out for possible predators lurking nearby.</Part7A1>
		<Part7A2>We have incoming! Try to scare them away with Herschel’s sonar ping.</Part7A2>
		<Part7A3>Defend the creature</Part7A3>
	if(creature == dead){ Mission Over}
	if(creature == survives){ Mission Continues}
		<Part7A4>I believe that is the last of them. Wait… look.</Part7A4>
		<Part8>[The creature’s mother appears and goes to the creature, MROWMRAR. 
			Communication between mother and offspring occurs.</Part8>
		<Part9>Incredible. Looks like the creature is in good hands, 
			now that it appears to be back back with its mother. 
			Excellent work.<Part10>
		<Part10>Accolade Achieved: “Guardian Angel”</Part10>
		

	<Part7B>CHOICE 2: It is better to let evolution take its own course and not interfere.<Part7B>
		<Part7C>I’m sorry, but there was nothing we can do. The creature’s life signs have stopped.</Part7C>
		<Part7C>The creature has died. MISSION OVER.</Part7C>


  </Parts>
  <!-- This mission requires you to make a decision -->
</Item>