<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Item>
	<Name id = 0002 "Cyrovolcano Quest"</Name>
	<Type> Scanning and Following Quest</Type>
	<Description>
		Recent seismic activity has TEC scratching there heads. Tectonic shifts or an explosion
		of some sort, there seems to be danger looming in the shadows. The player will be 
		finding what this seismic activity really is, a cyrovolcano.
	<Description>
	<Parts>
		</Part1>Camera shakes, loud explosions are heard in the distance.</Part2>
		</Part2>We are getting readings of seismic activity reading 9.2 on the
			Richter Scale not to far from you. We are not quite sure what is causing
			this jump, but we need you to investigate for any activity.</Part1>
		</Part3>Go to area of seismic activity and investigate.</Part3>
		</Part4>After doing further tests, we have ruled out any tectonic shifts,
			for the disturbance orginated above ground. There are two current
			possibilities for these readings, a asteroid impact or an eruption
			from Titan's crust. Scan the general area for impact zones or high levels
			of ammonia and nitrogen that could have been expelled from the crust.</Part4>
		</Part5>Collect rock samples in the area (0/5)</Part5>
		</Part6>The materials scanned show high levels of ammonia and nitrogen, pointing
			toward evidence of a explosion from Titan's crust. Investigate the surrounding
			area for the source of this explosion, the data we could collect would be
			priceless.</Part6>
		</Part7>Find where this explosion of ammonia and nitrogen is coming from</Part7>
		</Part8>It seems you have discovered a cryovolcano and it looks to be what was 
			causing that seismic activity. Collect samples at the base of the volcano but be 
			careful; if one of those rocks hit the probe, it could compromise the hull.</Part8>
		</Part9>Gather samples at the base of the cyrovolcano (0/2)</Part9>
		</Part10>We just received the data from the scans now. This information will help
			us further understand Titan's crust and all of its mysteries.</Part10>
	</Parts>
</Item>